You know, I'm thinking
about letting Emma have
her first cookie.
Her first cookie?
She has cookies all the time.
I've never given her a cookie.
Have you?
No.
No. And for the record,
I've also never given her
frosting from a can.
MONICA:
Hey, Rach,
the adoption agency needs
letters of recommendation,
and we were wondering if
you would write one for us.
Of course.
I'd be honored.
Thanks.
Thank you.
( clearing throat )
I think there's been
an oversight.
Joe, we would have
asked you.
We just thought
you wouldn't be interested.
Yeah, it's just that
we don't think of you
as really being so
much with the words.
Wha-wha, hey, wai-hey,
whoa, hey!
Clearly, we were wrong.
Look, I got a lot of nice stuff
to say about you guys, okay?
And I know how much
you want to have a baby,
and I would love
to help you get one.
You know what?
Then, Joey, we
want you to do it.
Thank you.
All right, let me see
how I'm going to start.
"Dear Baby Adoption
Decider People..."
So excited
about your letter.
Hey.
( greetings all around )
MONICA:
Wow, don't you
look nice?
Yes, I do.
Today's, uh, Mike and my
one-year anniversary.
Oh, what's it
the anniversary of?
Your first, uh, date,
your first kiss,
first time you had sex?
Yeah!
So, you must be going
somewhere fancy to celebrate.
Uh-huh.
Um, a Knicks game.
Uh... aren't you a
little overdressed?
Hey, you know what?
I've never had
a one-year anniversary before,
so no matter where we go,
I'm wearing
something fancy-pants,
and I'm going
to put on my finest jewelry,
and we're going to have sex
in a public restroom.
You guys do that?
Chandler won't even have
sex in our bathroom.
That's where people
make number two.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Mmm...
( chuckling )
So, you know,
I have a little time
if you, uh, if you want to...
Oh.
Oh, I'd love to,
but I really have
to grade these papers.
Oh!
Fine. That's fine.
I'll just shower by myself.
"B, B, B, B, B."
( chuckling )
Uh, Ross, you gave a "B"
to a Pottery Barn catalogue.
Well, it had
some good ideas.
Take off your shirt.
( chuckling )
( knock at door )
Damn it.
AMY:
Rachel? Open up.
It's your sister.
( knocking )
I have to
talk to you.
Hi, Amy.
You're not Rachel.
Still sharp as a tack.
Um, Charlie,
this is Rachel's sister, Amy,
Amy, this is Charlie.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Hi. And you are...?
Ross.
I, uh, I grew up
on your block.
We had Thanksgiving together
last year.
I had a baby with your sister.
No...
Did I buy a falafel from you
yesterday?
Yes, yes, you did.
Hi, Rachel.
Here's your sister,
Amy.
She thinks
I need pec implants.
Amy? Hi!
( chuckling )
Oh, you remember Joey?
Yeah. Hey, sure--
The Days of
Our Lives guy.
That's right, yeah.
You are not good.
Always nice to meet a fan.
So, now,
what are you doing here?
Well, I have huge news.
( Emma crying )
Oh, sorry, hold on,
let me just check on the baby.
Wait, this is important.
Can't Ella wait?
Uh, her name is Emma.
Why did you change it?
Ella was so much prettier.
What do I know?
I just sell
Middle-Eastern
food from a cart.
Hey, your English
is getting better.
Oh, my God.
I know.
She may be the hottest girl
I've ever hated.
What you...
what you working on?
Oh, Monica and Chandler's
recommendation.
I want it to sound smart,
but I don't know any big words,
or anything, so...
Well, why don't you
use your thesaurus?
What'd I just say?
Watch.
Here, you, uh,
you highlight
the word you
want to change,
go under "tools,"
and the thesaurus
generates-- gives--
...gives a whole
list of choices.
You can pick the word
that sounds smartest.
Oh. Oh, my God, that's great.
I'm smart!
No, no, I'm...
brainy, bright, clever.
I love this thing!
Look out, ladies,
Joey Tribbiani's
got the whole package!
God--
so beautiful.
Oh, I know, isn't she?
No, I was talking
about your bedding.
Oh... gosh.
All right,
what's your news, Amy?
Oh...
( clearing throat )
Well, I'm getting married.
Wha...?
Oh, my God! To who?
This guy.
Oh, oh...
He has a killer apartment.
And...?
And it's on Fifth.
And the elevator opens up
right into the living room.
No, what's he...
what's he like?
Oh, he's okay.
Do you remember
my old boyfriend, Mark?
Yeah.
It's his dad.
Huh.
Wow, so, he's
got to be...
Old? Yeah.
But he travels a lot,
so he's hardly ever there.
Sweetie, I got to tell you,
it sounds a little bit
like you like the apartment
more than you like...
Myron.
Yeah, I told you he was old.
Oh... sit
down, sit down.
What?
Oh, honey, you know,
I once also almost
married somebody
that I didn't love.
Do you remember Barry?
Remember him?
God, we used to make out
all the time
after you
went to sleep.
Yeah, sometimes
just nodding is okay.
Um, but anyway, listen.
Not marrying Barry
was the best decision
that I ever, ever made.
Honey, Amy,
you-you deserve true love.
Your-your soul mate
is out there somewhere--
someone that is your age,
that is smart,
that is fun,
and that-that
you care about.
You're right.
I'm-I'm going to do it.
Okay.
I'm going to marry Myron
and keep looking for Mr. Right.
Okay.
Okay, let's keep talking.
Excuse me.
Our anniversary.
Anniversary.
Um, yeah. Sir,
could you...
could you move your nachos?
They're in my seat.
It's my anniversary.
Here we are.
Can't believe it's
been a whole year.
I know.
This has been the best year...
( crowd cheering )
( yelling ):
This has been
the best year of my life!
( yelling ):
Me, too!
I never thought I could
love someone this much!
I feel the same way!
You're so generous and kind,
( cheering dies down )
and you're amazing in bed!
It's...
It's our anniversary.
ANNOUNCER:
Knicks fans,
can you please turn your
attention to the scoreboard?
Someone has
a very special question to ask.
( crowd groans sympathetically
and applauds )
Oh, how lame.
Oh, it's so tacky
and impersonal.
Really?
Oh, it's the worst
way to propose.
Excuse me.
Hey, I finished
my recommendation. Here.
Uh, I think
you'll be very, very happy.
It was the longest
I ever spent on a computer
without looking at porn.
I don't, uh, understand.
Some of the words a little
too sophisticated for you?
It doesn't
make any sense.
Of course it does.
It's smart.
I used a thesaurus.
On every word?
Yup.
All right, what was
this sentence originally?
Oh, "They are warm, nice people
with big hearts."
And that became,
"They are humid,
prepossessing Homo Sapiens...
with full-sized aortic pumps."
Yeah, yeah, and hey,
I really mean it, dude.
Hey, Joey, I don't
think we can use this.
Why not?
Well, because
You signed it
"Baby Kangaroo" Tribbiani.
Honey, why don't
you stop worrying
about sounding smart
and just be yourself?
You know what?
you don't need a thesaurus.
Just write from here--
your full-sized aortic pump.
Amy, hi.
I took your advice.
I left Myron.
Oh, good for you!
I know.
I'm Erin Brockovich!
Yes, you are.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Oh, thank you.
So, can I stay with you?
But... Erin Brockovich
had her own house.
Please?
( chuckling ):
Uh, look who's back.
Why do you have bags?
Rach, why does
she have bags?!
Well, I'm staying with you guys.
What?!
We're going to be roomies!
Come on.
You slept out here?
Well, Amy kept kicking
me in her sleep,
yelling, "Myron, get off."
But, uh, we're getting rid
of her, right?
Rach, please tell me
we're getting rid of her.
Joey, I can't do that.
Oh, come on!
Last night I was
finishing off a pizza,
and she said,
"A moment on the lips,
forever on the hips."
I don't need that kind
of talk in my house!
Well, Joey,
look, I know
that she's difficult,
but I think it's really good
that she's here.
'Cause we'll appreciate
it more when she's gone?
I, wh...?
No, it's just,
look, you know,
when I first moved to this city,
I was a lot like her.
I was spoiled, self-centered,
and you guys
really took care of me.
Yeah, Monica made us.
Well, whatever,
I really appreciate it,
'cause I don't think I would be
the person that I am today
if it wasn't for you guys.
See, I want to help Amy
the way you guys helped me,
and I know it's going to take
patience, but that's okay.
Good morning.
( groans )
RACHEL:
Amy,
that what I was supposed
to wear today.
That's why I hung it
on the door.
Oh, sweetie,
you can't pull this off.
Amy, you know what,
I was thinking that, um,
maybe now would be
a good time for us
to sit down
and, uh, you know,
talk about your future.
Oh, I can't, honey.
I'm going to go
get my eyebrows shaped.
I am not happy.
Uh.
Sure you want
to eat that?
I'm curvy and I like it!
Hi.
Hey.
I just I had
the worst anniversary ever.
CHANDLER:
I doubt that.
Tell her about us last year.
Oh, well, I bought Chandler
a $500 watch,
and he wrote me a rap song.
Seriously?
Word.
Well, mine was worse than that.
Well, what happened?
We were at the game, and this
guy proposed to his girlfriend
on the big screen thing.
Oh, that is so tacky.
Well, that's what I said.
But it turns out Mike
was planning on proposing to me
that same way last night.
Oh, my God.
Mike was going to propose?
Phoebe, that's huge.
Well, do you want
to marry him?
Yeah, I really do, yes.
But after I dumped on the way
he was going to propose to me,
I don't think he's ever going
to ask again.
I mean, I said no in Barbados,
and now this.
She's right.
If I were a guy and...
Did I just say,
"If I were a guy"?
Maybe you don't need him
to propose to you.
Maybe you could propose to him.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
Isn't that a little desperate?
I proposed to Chandler.
All right, moving on.
Well, I don't think
it was desperate.
I think it was amazing.
Thank you.
Well, do you think
I should propose?
I think it could
be kind of great.
Absolutely.
You'll love the feeling.
There's nothing like it.
Okay. Okay.
So, how should I do it?
How about at a game
on the big screen?
( gasps ):
How about at
a Foot Locker?
What? What,
he obviously thinks
that's a nice way
to be proposed to.
Plus, he'd never suspect it.
Yeah, that does
make sense. Okay.
Now, would-would you two
like that?
Sounds good to me.
But what would a guy think?
Uh, Nana's on the phone.
Oh, that's interesting,
since she died seven years ago.
She did?
Who got her condo in Boca?
Hello.
Oh.
It's our nanny.
Hi.
Oh, God, I hope
you feel better.
Okay, bye.
That's Molly, she's sick.
Can you watch Emma today?
I can't. I have
back-to-back classes.
Did Molly say what she had
because my throat's
been hurting.
Menstrual cramps.
I don't think
that's what this is.
Can any of you watch Emma?
No, sorry.
No, sorry, sweetie.
No, I've got work,
and then I'm proposing and...
Oh, great.
Shoot! What are we going to do?
Well, I could do it.
Well, actually...
Uh, can I talk to you
for a sec?
Yeah.
Um, I do not want her
baby-sitting our child.
Why not?
Well, for one thing,
she keeps calling her "Ella."
Ella's a nice name.
Fine, we'll call
the next one Ella!
Next, the next one?
Okay, uh...
Um, I don't want her
watching our baby.
Ross, I am trying to help
her become a better person.
This is a huge
breakthrough for her.
She just offered
to do something
for another human being.
Look, look,
I-I don't know...
Ross, I'm telling you,
she's giving up getting
her eyebrows shaped
to do this, all right?
Do you understand
how important that is
in our world?
Um, listen, I...
I couldn't help but overhear
'cause I was trying to.
Listen,
let me do this.
I-I really want
to help you guys out,
and plus, Rachel's been
so wonderful to me.
Absolutely.
Oh, great.
So, how much does it pay?
Hey, Joe.
How's the second draft
of the letter coming?
Great. I'm finished.
In fact,
I just dropped it off
at the agency.
You dropped it off?
Yeah.
Can we read it?
Can you print out
another copy?
No can do, amigo.
No, I didn't use a computer.
It felt more personal
to handwrite it.
( groans )
You handwrote it?
Yeah, and don't worry.
I didn't try to sound smart
at all.
See you later.
Oh, my God.
That letter is going
to go in our file.
We're never going
to get a kid.
No, we're gonna...
we're gonna be
one of those old couples
that collects orchids
or-or has a lot of birds.
It's okay. It's okay.
You know what,
I will just call the agency
and tell them
to throw out the letter.
Okay, good.
Hello.
This is Chandler Bing.
Somebody just dropped off
a handwritten
recommendation letter and...
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Thank you.
Good-bye.
Oh, we're screwed, aren't we?
You know what, just tell me
on the way to the bird store.
They loved it.
What?
They thought
it was very smart of us
to have a child write
the recommendation letter.
They thought
Joey was a child?
She guessed eight, nine,
based on his drawings.
AMY:
Hi.
MONICA:
Hey, what did you guys do today?
Ella wanted to go out,
so we went shopping
and got some sushi.
That sounds like fun.
Yeah, not really.
Babies are dull.
Hey.
Hi. How's my girl?
I'm fine.
And...
I got you a present for
letting me stay with you.
Ready?
Yes.
Ta-da!
You pierced her ears?
Doesn't it make her
nose look smaller?
( shrieks )
How could you do this
without telling me?
Well, if I had told you,
then it wouldn't have been
a surprise, now, would it?
( moans )
I think she looks cute.
But I am wrong.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
here comes Ross.
He is going to flip out.
Why, did something happen
to his falafel cart?
Hey, guys.
Hi, Ross.
Ross.
Hi, Emma.
Oh, why is she wearing her hat
so low?
She can barely see.
I don't really
want her to see.
Why not?
MONICA:
Well, because
there's so many terrible sights
in this world.
Like war.
Or that thing in Joey's
refrigerator, remember?
It was in a milk carton,
but it looked like meat?
Come here. Come here.
( gasps )
There she is.
Hi.
What?
Nothing.
Hi.
Wh...?
( gasping )
Please tell me
those are clip-ons.
Oh, they're real.
Did she do this to her?
I told you we shouldn't
have left Emma with her.
I know, I know,
and you were
right, Ross, okay?
You are so irresponsible!
I am never letting you
baby-sit ever again!
Hey, you know, what,
this kid needs me, okay?
She needs to have
a cool, fun aunt.
I'm a cool, fun aunt.
Okay.
Hey!
Monica can be cool and fun
at organized, indoor projects!
I cannot believe this.
All I wanted to do was
help you try to figure out
what to do with your life,
and this is how
you repay me?!
Well, I don't need you
to help me
because I already know what
I'm going to do with my life.
Oh, yeah? Since when?
Since today.
I am going to be a baby stylist.
What?
That's not a thing!
Well, it should be.
I'm going to help babies
learn how to accessorize,
what colors to wear,
what clothes are slimming.
Babies don't care
if they're slim!
Enter Amy.
Amy, I j... I just...
I just want to...
What? What are you doing to do?
No more falafel for you!
Oh, great game, huh?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Why do you keep
looking at the screen?
I'm not.
I-I'm praying.
Please,
let the Knicks win.
Thank you, Thor.
Where are you going?
Going to go to
the bathroom.
Well, I think
you should wait.
Why?
Well, if you don't...
if you don't hold it in,
you don't... you don't get
all the nutrients.
ANNOUNCER:
Knicks fans,
can we turn your attention
to the big screen.
Someone has a special question
to ask.
Mike Hannigan,
will you marry me?
ANNOUNCER
Get a load of this.
She's proposing to him.
Guess we know who wears
the pants in that family.
Well, that's not
very enlightened!
( crowd booing )
Wuss!
Wimp!
Hey! Hey!
Boo us? Boo you!
( crowd booing )
( phone rings )
Hello?
Yeah, this is Joey Tribbiani.
Oh, hi.
Well, I'm glad
you liked my letter.
No, my mommy and daddy
aren't home right now.
Okay, bye-bye.
She was nice.
Joey, get Amy's bags.
She is moving out.
Whoo-hoo!
You're kicking me out?
You put holes in my baby's ears.
Yeah, well, at least now people
will know she's a girl.
( gasps )
I can't believe
I ever even tried
to help you.
You are so beyond help.
You know what,
ever since I got here,
you have been nothing
but negative.
Excuse me?
You didn't want me
to marry the old guy
with the great apartment.
Then, I try
to help your daughter
de-emphasize her flaws...
...and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
Joey, where are those bags?
JOEY:
She has a lot of crap!
( groans )
You know what?
When I moved in here, I thought,
this is going to be so great.
Just us sisters,
back together again,
like when we were kids,
except without that stupid Jill.
Oh, who has gotten fat,
by the way.
Seriously?
Mm-hmm.
Mom said she gained,
like, 15 pounds.
Hips or thighs?
Ass and face.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I thought she was on Atkins.
She was.
Carbs found her.
See?
This is what I wanted.
Two sisters talking
about real stuff.
Oh, I can give you that.
You can?
Yeah.
I kept trying to make
you a better person,
but you're, you're already
a pretty perfect version
of what you are.
Thank you.
And you've got to admit,
Emma does look cute.
Did you just say "Emma"?
Oh, I'm sorry. Ella.
That woman at the
game didn't know
what she was
talking about, Mike.
Obviously,
you have balls.
Well, please, let's just forget
the whole thing.
I would love it.
Consider it forgotten.
Thank you.
But just so you know,
however and whenever
you decide to propose,
I promise I'll say yes.
Whether-whether, you know,
it's at a basketball game
or in skywriting
or, you know, like some
lame guy in a cheesy movie
who hides it in the cake.
It's in the cake, isn't it?
Where else would lame,
Mr. No Balls hide it?
What's the matter with me?
Why do I keep
ruining this?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, it's my fault.
I keep trying to propose
in these stupid ways,
and all I want to do
is tell you that I love you,
and that I want to spend the
rest of my life with you and...
I'm going to do this now.
Oh, my God.
Phoebe, I...
Wait, oh, wait.
Oh, no.
Okay. Ooh.
Ready?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Phoebe, I love you.
There's no one else
in the world
I would ask to marry me
three times.
But I want
to take care of you,
have babies with you...
...and grow old with you.
Phoebe Buffay,
will you marry me?
Yes.
I love you.
I love you more.
Not possible.
She's going to be
Mrs. No Balls.
So, how's the, uh,
baby-styling business going?
Not that great.
It's... it's almost
as if people
don't want to hear that
their babies are ugly.
That's shocking.
I know.
Uh, there's Ross.
Hey, Ross.
Hello! Ross!
( scoffs )
He's rude.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org